http://www.krishna.com/privacy-policy

ABOUTLANGUAGESArabicPortugueseSpanishSimplified ChineseTraditional ChineseSIGN IN
HomeAbout UsContact UsNewslettersFounderBBTDonateOpportunitiesAbout KrishnaKrishna the PersonKrishna ConsciousnessOverviewTopic IndexGlossaryThe Reading RoomBhagavad-gitaMagazineAssorted Q and ABooksCatalog of TitlesBhagavad-gita As It IsSrimad BhagavatamCaitanya CaritamritaAudiobooksEbooksOther BooksBTG MagazineAudioAudiobooksLecturesLiveMusicRadioStoriesKirtanVideosSrila PrabhupadaMantra MeditationDocumentariesKrishna PeopleHow-ToSaintsTVWebcamsArtPaintingsPhotosMoreBlogsISKCONMagazineTemplesLinksKids' PlaygroundFestivals & EventsFoodPrabhupadaEducationStoreBooksAudio & VideoHome TempleArtMeditationGiftsApparelKid's ShopBargainsStore Help
Home
Privacy Policy
Definitions and General Statement
Collection
Cookies
Usage
Third Parties
Children (Minors)
Security
Removal or Update of Personal Information
1. Definitions and General Statement
The Bhaktivedanta Book Trust International (BBTI) and its website, Krishna.com (hereafter referred to as "we", "us", "our") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of Personal Information collected about our Users (hereafter referred to as "you", "your"). We do not sell or otherwise disclose any individually identifiable Personal Information about you without your express and informed consent, unless required by law.
2. Collection
We collect your Personal Information where necessary during e-mail and site registration, store purchases, and other user registration processes. In addition, we collect statistical non-personally identifiable information from you in the form of usage data (for example, length of session, pages viewed, geographical location, etc.) for use as stated in the paragraph on "Usage" below.
3. Cookies
"Cookies" are industry standard, non-personally identifiable pieces of information that the we temporarily transfer to your computer to enhance your viewing and shopping experience. We use Cookies to provide you with seamless access to the Krishna.com Store, to temporarily store items in your shopping cart for the duration of the checkout period, and to authorize you to log into your account and make transactions. (Note: Browsers set to provide notice when a Cookie is placed will prompt you to accept or reject the Cookies.)
4. Usage
We believe in protecting your privacy. To that end, we use "double opt-in" collection methods to allow you to choose to send us your information for specific, stated purposes. If you ever feel you have received an email from us in error, or wish to unsubscribe from an e-mail service you've signed up for, please contact us.
We use statistical, non-identifiable user information in the aggregate (such as geographical location, pages viewed, browser type, etc.) for improving the usability of Krishna.com.
We use Personal Information such as your e-mail address to provide you with specifically requested services, such as e-mail news about
our Site, "daily meditations", or promotional offers for our Krishna.com Store products. We reserve the right to, on rare occasions but when necessary, send important e-mail announcements about Krishna.com to all Users, such as but not limited to, changes in services, changes of terms, or major site upgrades.
At the Krishna.com Store, we use Personal Information for the sole purpose of providing you with services requested. For example, to fulfill your product order and transact associated payments. We do not share Personal Information with third parties unless required by law (for example, in criminal investigations.)
For your protection, all sensitive transactions at the Krishna.com Store are conducted using state-of-the-art encryption technology on secure servers.
To unsubscribe from any service offered by Krishna.com, you can contact us at any time.
5. Third Parties
We sometimes use statistical non-personally identifiable demographic information about our Users in the aggregate (such as the number of unique visitors to our site, hits, most visited pages, etc.) in connection with our marketing programs. However, we do not disclose identifiable Personal Information about you without your express consent, unless required by law. In addition, you may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us.
6. Children (Minors)
Children (Minors) should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any Personal Information to us. You must be 18 years or older, as required by law, to transact business and purchase items from our site. We expressly adhere to all laws and policies related to children's privacy.
7. Security
We only collect Personal Information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we use state-of-the-art security technology to ensure the security, integrity, safety, encryption, and privacy of any sensitive Personal Information (for example, while making a purchase at our Krishna.com Store).
While we make all reasonable attempts to secure your Personal Information, we will not be held responsible for any involuntary breach of our security, and any actions by third parties resulting therefrom, such as but not limited to computer or internet hacking, equipment malfunction, acts of God, war, civil unrest, and any other causes beyond our reasonable control.
8. Removal or Update of Personal Information
You may update or remove your Personal Information from our records via any of the means listed below. Please be sure to include the following information in your correspondence:
Your e-mail address
Your first and last name
The service or section of the site to which you are registered or subscribed.
Via E-mail Form.
Via fax: 386-462-1761
Via postal mail:
Krishna.com
Dept: Customer Service
P.O. Box 430
Alachua, FL 32616
USA
For additional information, please also read our Terms and Conditions of Use for Krishna.com.
54017 reads
Join our family of supporters. Make a donation.
Thank you to the following individuals for keeping Krishna.com alive and vibrant:
Ajitkumar Agrawal, Alfred Fitch, Amit N, Amit Singh, Ankit Bansal, Arun Athithan, Ashim Kumar Kar, Ashley Dalke, Audrey Jimenez, Bhaskar Gurram, Bhavanaben Desai, Bhavin Thakker, Brian Bloch, Carmen Rodriguez, Chetan Suri, Chirag Mahyavanshi, David Corcoran III, David Taylor, Dev Mani, Edita Vasiljeviene, Edward Easterling, Francisco Picazo, Gary Mark, Gary Sund, Genevieve Brewster, Ian Lubsey, Jai Devaki Parks, Jonathan Maxwell, Joseph Milosch, Jurga Saule, Keith Fralin, Lorraine Groom, Lotus Imprints, Luz Ramirez, Mahipal Reddy Patolla, Margot Cordua, Marina Hansen Russo, Marlon Brock, Martin Rosenthal, Narendra Kumar, Nila Khurana, Partha Bose, Pratapa Reddy Dokuru, Prinul Gunputh, Renuka Muthumanickam, Robert Goettler, Rosa Wallace, Sam Clements, Samit Misra, Saranagati International, Shalini Anand, Sharon Standley, Shyamal Krishna, Smitha Konduri, Sreedhar Segu, Stephen Kenton, Sumit Patel, Sundari Rodman, Sunilkumar Patel, Supriya Sengupta, Surendra Krishnan, Tessa Gordon, Thirumalesh Bhat, Venkat Krishnan, Veronika Ward, Vijay Patel, Vijay Varanasi, Vikas Manna, Vishal Gandotra, Viswanadh Musunuri, Yuvaraj C Thandu
Home
About Us
Contact Us
Newsletters
Founder
BBT
Donate
Opportunities
Copyright © 2002-2021 The Bhaktivedanta Book Trust International, Inc. All rights reserved. | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy
